You probably know that Alex is a very serious mathematician and he likes to solve serious problems. This is another problem from Alex.
You are given three nonnegative integers a, b, c. 
You have to arrange them in some order and put +, − or × signs between them to minimize the outcome of the resulting expression. 
You are not allowed to use unary minus and parentheses in the expression. There must be exactly one sign between every pair of neighbouring numbers. 
You should use standard order for performing operations (multiplication first, addition and subtraction then).

----------------------------------------------------------------

The constraints are pretty small .. .they are all positive numbers.

Without loss of generality, let a <= b <= c

We aren't allowed to use unary minus ...

The answer is min(a - (b + c), a - b*c).

Proof ....

Since a is the smallest number, both these expressions yield a negative number. 
This means we can neglect all combinations consisting only of + and *. 

Since unary - is not allowed, the minimum expression is gotten by subtracting the maximum amount from a ... 

There is only one situation when a- (b +c) is smaller than a - b*c , when a = b =c = 1.

Otherwise, answer is always a - b*c ...because b*c is the greatest amount that can be subtracted from a.

--------------------------------------------------

#define min_3(a, b, c) min(a, min(b, c) )
#define max_3(a, b, c) max(a, max(b, c) )

using namespace std;

int main()
{
    int a, b, c, answer;
    scanf("%d %d %d", &a, &b, &c);

    int x = min_3(a, b, c);
    int y = max_3(a, b, c);
    int z = (a + b + c) - (x + y);

    answer = min(x - (y*z), x - (y + z));

    printf("%d\n", answer);

    return 0;
}
-----------------------------------------------

Note, the time limit of timus is very strict .. I got a TLE when I sorted(a, b, c) by calling STL sort. 