You have a number of stones with known weights w1, …, wn. 
Write a program that will rearrange the stones into two piles such that weight difference between the piles is minimal.
Input
Input contains the number of stones n (1 ≤ n ≤ 20) and weights of the stones w1, …, wn (integers, 1 ≤ wi ≤ 100000) delimited by white spaces.
Output
Your program should output a number representing the minimal possible weight difference between stone piles.

--------------------------------------------

My first approach was to adopt a greedy approach ... Sort the weights ... Place the heaviest weight in group 1. Next heaviest in group 2 ... 
Place the heaviest unplaced weight in the lighter group ..

However, this does not work and is not the optimal strategy.

Consider the case - 9, 9, 9, 13, 14 ... The minimum difference in 0 ... But, my strategy does - {14, 9}, {13, 9, 9} with a difference of 8.

----------------------------------

The constraints are small enough to brute force and check every possible partition ... N is at most 20 ... So we brute force using bitmasks...

Consider a binary string of length N ... If the i-th digit is 0, then we place the i-th weight in the first group, and in the second group if the i-th bit is 1.

Thus, there is a bijection between binary strings of length N and and partitioning into two subsets.

There are 2^N binary strings ... But we ignore the string of all 0s ... So, we use the bitmask from 1 to 2^n - 1.

Check which bits are set from 0 till N-1 ... Put the set bit elements in one set and the rest in another.

--------------------------------------

This only works because of the extremely small constraint.

----------------------------------------

int main() 
{
	const int INFINITY = 1e9 + 1;
	int number_of_piles, min_difference = INFINITY;
	scanf("%d", &number_of_piles);
	
	vector <int> weight(number_of_piles);
	for(int i = 0; i < number_of_piles; i++)
		scanf("%d", &weight[i]);
	
	//N can be at most 20 ... This allows brute force checking
	int no_of_bitmasks = (1 << number_of_piles) - 1; 
	for(int bitmask = 1; bitmask <= no_of_bitmasks; bitmask++)
	{
		int sum_1 = 0, sum_2 = 0;
		for(int i = 0; i < number_of_piles; i++)
		{
			if( (bitmask & (1 << i)) == 0)
				sum_1 += weight[i];
			else
				sum_2 += weight[i];
		}
		
		min_difference = min(min_difference, abs(sum_1 - sum_2));
	}
	
	printf("%d\n", min_difference);
	return 0;
}